# **COREY NANCE**

Salem, NH 03079 | EMAIL-COREYNANCE83@GMAIL.COM | 781-426-1186 https://www.linkedin.com/in/corey-nance-87139841

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Previous car sales consultant for a little over 13 years, high level of success by maintaining a perfect 100 customer satisfaction score while averaging 25 car sales a month. These achievements allowed me to make the top 100 sales consultant list in the Northeast Business Center. Next family-oriented move, to be a Motor Coach driver for a little over 3 years. While on this job I received countless praise for my professionalism with riders and my camaraderie with co-workers. These achievements attributed to the company's consideration for an Operations Manager Position within that short time. All while attending school at SNHU to get my bachelor's degree in Software Engineering which I currently maintain a GPA of 3.96 and attend UNH's Coding Bootcamp for software development.

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

- Automotive mechanics as a hobby
- Extensive Sales experience
- Extensive Product Knowledge in the automotive field
- Great Customer Service
- Entry level C++
- Entry level Java
- Entry level Python
- Entry level JavaScript
- Entry level HTML/CSS

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science**

Present

Southern New Hampshire University Manchester, NH

• GPA: 4.0

## **Coding Bootcamp for Full Stack Software Development**

Present

University of New Hampshire Portsmouth, NH

• Grade A+

#### RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Motor Coach Driver**

Sep 2016 - Sep 2016

Boston Express Bus Londonderry, NH

 To inspect and operate a Motor Coach in the safest manner With up to 51 passengers on board

## **Sales Consultant**

Jan 2016 - Sep 2016

Clark Chrysler Jeep Dodge Ram Methuen, MA

• Had the opportunity to become a Motor Coach Driver

Service Advisor Aug 2012 - Nov 2012

Lawless Dodge Chrysler Jeep Woburn, MA

• Help customers through getting their cars fixed in a professional

**Sales Consultant** Oct 2007 - Aug 2012

Kelly Jeep Chrysler Lynnfield, MA

• Help customers obtain the right vehicle for their needs

**Owner Operator** 

Auto quip of New England Salem, NH

• Business Partner

Apr 2015 - Jan 2016